//Here we are creaging an array that will include the questions, four available options and the answer for each question, this array will be used in the main JS file which will function the quiz
var mainQuestions =[{
	"Question": "How was the mascot of Euro 2016 called?",
	"Option1": "La Victoire",
	"Option2": "Super Victor",
	"Option3": "Driblou",
	"Option4": "Goalix",
	"Answer":"2"
},{
	"Question": "Who scored the first goal of Euro 2016?",
	"Option1": "Paul Pogba",
	"Option2": "Dimitri Payet",
	"Option3": "Antoine Griezmann",
	"Option4": "Olivier Giroud",
	"Answer": "4"
},{
	"Question": "Which country shook the Euro 2016 after winning against Enlgand?",
	"Option1": "Iceland",
	"Option2": "France",
	"Option3": "Ireland",
	"Option4": "Switzerland",
	"Answer": "1"
},{
	"Question": "Which country did Portugal beat in order to advance to the Semi-Finals?",
	"Option1": "Germany",
	"Option2": "Romania",
	"Option3": "Poland",
	"Option4": "France",
	"Answer": "3"
},{
	"Question": "Whose stunning overhead kick for Switzerland sent their round-of-16 tie against Poland into extra time?",
	"Option1": "Haris Seferovic",
	"Option2": "Xherdan Shaqiri",
	"Option3": "Granit Xhaka",
	"Option4": "Breel Embolo",
	"Answer": "2"
},{
	"Question": "Whose own goal settled the round-of-16 tie between Wales and Northern Ireland?",
	"Option1": "Paddy McNair",
	"Option2": "Gareth McAuley",
	"Option3": "Jonny Evans",
	"Option4": "Conor McLaughlin",
	"Answer": "2"
},{
	"Question": "Who was the only team to fail to score a goal at the Euros?",
	"Option1": "Albania",
	"Option2": "Czach republic",
	"Option3": "Austria",
	"Option4": "Ukraine",
	"Answer": "4"
},{
	"Question": "Whose handball gifted France a penalty in their semi-finals clash against Germany?",
	"Option1": "Toni Kroos",
	"Option2": "Bastain Schweinsteinger",
	"Option3": "Jerome Boateng",
	"Option4": "Benedikt Howedes",
	"Answer": "2"
},{
	"Question": "Who had the most shots on target at euro 2016?",
	"Option1": "Wayne Rooney",
	"Option2": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
	"Option3": "Gareth Bale",
	"Option4": "Antoine Griezmann",
	"Answer": "3"
},{
	"Question": "Who won the Euro 2016?",
	"Option1": "Portugal",
	"Option2": "Enlgand",
	"Option3": "Spain",
	"Option4": "France",
	"Answer": "1"
},{
	"Question": "When did the Euro 2016 begin?",
	"Option1": "Jun 10, 2016",
	"Option2": "Jul 10, 2016",
	"Option3": "Jul 3, 2016",
	"Option4": "Jun 14, 2016",
	"Answer": "1"
},{
	"Question": "Who scored the winnig goal for Portugal in the final?",
	"Option1": "Éder",
	"Option2": "Nani",
	"Option3": "Renato Sanches",
	"Option4": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
	"Answer": "1"
},{
	"Question": "How many goals were scored overall in the Euros 2016?",
	"Option1": "94",
	"Option2": "59",
	"Option3": "108",
	"Option4": "163",
	"Answer": "3"
},{
	"Question": "Which country had the highest possession on the field while playing?",
	"Option1": "Enlgand",
	"Option2": "Ukraine",
	"Option3": "Spain",
	"Option4": "Germany",
	"Answer": "4"
},{
	"Question": "What was the opening match of the Euros?",
	"Option1": "France vs Romania",
	"Option2": "Wales vs Slovakia",
	"Option3": "Enlgand vs Russia",
	"Option4": "Germany vs Albania",
	"Answer": "1"
},{
	"Question": "How far did Ireland progress?",
	"Option1": "Semi-Finals",
	"Option2": "Quarter-Finals",
	"Option3": "Final",
	"Option4": "Round-of-16",
	"Answer": "4"
},{
	"Question": "Which country hosted the Euro 2016?",
	"Option1": "Poland",
	"Option2": "Russia",
	"Option3": "France",
	"Option4": "Enlgand",
	"Answer": "3"
},{
	"Question": "How many goals did Cristiano Ronaldo score in qualifying for Euro 2016?",
	"Option1": "11",
	"Option2": "7",
	"Option3": "5",
	"Option4": "9",
	"Answer": "3"
},{
	"Question": "Who was the fastes runner in the Euro 2016?",
	"Option1": "Richárd Guzmics",
	"Option2": "Jonny Evans",
	"Option3": "Kingsley Coman",
	"Option4": "Dragos Grigore",
	"Answer": "3"
},{
	"Question": "Which country's goalkeeper saved the most goals?",
	"Option1": "Northern Ireland",
	"Option2": "Belgium",
	"Option3": "Hungary",
	"Option4": "Iceland",
	"Answer": "4"
}];
